// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following is not a keyword in java?",
    answer: "Boolean",
    options: [
      "Static",
      "Boolean",
      "Void",
      "Private"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which is the final state in an Object Life-cycle?",
    answer: "Deallocated",
    options: [
      "Unused",
      "Collected",
      "Unreachable",
      "Deallocated"
      ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is the default value of char variable?",
    answer: "'\u0000'",
    options: [
      "'\u0000'",
      "0",
      "Null",
      "Not defined"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Method Overloading is an example of",
    answer: "Static Binding",
    options: [
      "Dynamic Binding",
      "Global Binding",
      "Static Binding",
      "None of the above"
      ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following is not a builtin datatype?",
    answer: "String",
    options: [
      "String",
      "Long",
      "Char",
      'Double'
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What is TreeSet Interface?",
    answer: "It is a Set implemented when we want elements in a sorted order.",
    options: [
      "It is a Set implemented when we want elements in a tree based order",
      "It is a Set implemented when we want elements in a sorted order",
      "It is a Set implemented when we want elements in a binary tree format",
      "It is a Set implemented when we want elements in a hiearchical order"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Dynamic binding uses which information for binding",
    answer: "Object",
    options: [
      "Type",
      "Object",
      "Both of the above",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What is runtime polymorphism?",
    answer: "Runtime polymorphism is a process in which a call to an overridden method is resolved at runtime rather than at compile-time",
    options: [
      "Runtime polymorphism is a process in which a call to an overridden method is resolved at runtime rather than at compile-time",
      "Runtime polymorphism is a process in which a call to an overloaded method is resolved at runtime rather than at compile-time.",
      "Both of the above",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is currentThread()?",
    answer: "It is a Thread public static method used to obtain a reference to the current thread",
    options: [
      "It is a thread's instance method used to get thread count",
      "It is a object's public static method used obtain a reference to the current thread",
      "It is a object's instance method used to get thread count",
      "It is a Thread public static method used to obtain a reference to the current thread"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following is a valid keyword?",
    answer: "Throw",
    options: [
      "Float",
      "Throw",
      "Try",
      "String"
    ]
  },

];